let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the leader of the Team 7?",
    answer: "kakashi",
    options: ["Iruka", "kakashi", "Azuma", "Kuranei"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "who is the 4th hokage?",
    answer: "Minato Namikaze",
    options: ["Lady Tsunade", "Kushina uzumaki", "Minato Namikaze", "Onoki"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "who is Gaara's first friend?",
    answer: "Naruto",
    options: ["Kankuro", "Shikamaaru", "Sasuke", "Naruto"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "who killed Iruka Sensei's parents?",
    answer: "kurama",
    options: ["Obito", "kurama", "Orochimaaru", "3rd Ninja War"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Who is Naruto's crush",
    answer: "Sakura",
    options: ["Hinata", "Tenten", "Temari", "Sakura"],
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the highest rank of Shinobi?",
    answer: "Kage",
    options: ["Jonin", "Kage", "Anbu Black Ops", "God"],
  },
 
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the Name of the Nine Tail Beast?",
    answer: "Kurama",
    options: ["Kurama", "Shikaku", "Son Goku", "Gyuki"],
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is also known as Surprising Ninja?",
    answer: "Naruto Uzumaki",
    options: ["Naruto Uzumaki", "Sasuke Uchiha", "Neji Hyuga", "Shino Aburame"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is also known as Copy Ninja?",
    answer: "Kakashi Hatake",
    options: ["Kakashi Hatake", "Tenten", "Might Guy", "Azuma Saratobi"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is also known as Last Uchiha?",
    answer: "Sasuke",
    options: ["Itachi", "Kakashi", "Obito", "Sasuke"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Who is from Saratobi Clan?",
    answer: "Konahamaru",
    options: ["Konahamaru", "Tenten", "Might Guy", "Fukaku"],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which jutsu is Entry level test to become a Genin",
    answer: "Clone",
    options: ["Clone", "Transformation", "Leaf Hurricane", "Beast Human Clone"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is the Naruto's First Student?",
    answer: "Konahamaru",
    options: ["Udon", "Moegi", "Konahamaru", "Ebisu"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What is the name of the Naruto's Class Teacher Name?",
    answer: "Iruka",
    options: ["Iruka", "Kakashi", "Azuma", "Kurenei"],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the Naruto's Favourite Food?",
    answer: "Ichiraku Ramen",
    options: ["Ichiraku Ramen", "Curry Rice", "Spegati", "None of the Above"],
  },

];